(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T22:39:57.826134",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
3D: March 26th, 2026 @studio. "DONT GET LOST AGAIN -kchan"
Hmmm... Am I lost again?
This door looks sus.
Should I... or should I not?
Dahlah.
Dahlah saja
Walk it off and go
Isn't this a thing that you're used to?
Disappointed and feeling blue
When the world doesn't go the way you want it to
And maybe now is just the perfect time
To let it go and just unwind
There's no need to ask why ever again
Just let it go, the answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it, just try to get through your day
Just let it go, then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes to get through the ache and still win the day
Dahlah saja, oh, dahlah saja
Walk it off and go
What else can you do?
When your feelings are barely there
Up to a point of pure despair
When you have given it your all, but ends in vain
Just let it go, the answer you've been looking for
No need to be sad about it, just try to get through your day
Just let it go, then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes to get through the ache and still win the day
Let life takes over the wheel
Let life take over the wheel
And shift it to higher gears
Then you will finally see
Just let it go
The answer you've been looking for
You dont need to be sad
You dont need to be mad
Just try to get through your day
Just let it go
Then maybe in the end you'll know
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
You got what it takes
To get through the ache
And still win the day
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
Dahlah saja
Just let it be
Oh, Dahlah saja
Oh, just let it be
Walk it off and go
ma ii ka
Well, whatever
Podcast sendiri, ya?
A podcast by myself?
Kaellooo~!
Let's go home~!
Nani?
What?
Apaan, tuh?
What's that?
Hmm... 9 lampu...
Hmm... nine lights...
Mic...
A mic...
headset...
a headset...
Content creator?
A content creator?
Eh...
Warnanya...
The colors...
hololive ID?!
Sahabat sejatiku
My true friend,
Hilangkah dari ingatanmu
has it faded from your memory?
Di hari kita saling berbagi
On the days we used to share...
Dengan kotak sejuta mimpi
...with a box of a million dreams,
Aku datang menghampirimu
I came to you,
Kuperlihatkan semua hartaku
to show you all my treasures.
Kita slalu berpendapat
We always believed
Kita ini yang terhebat
that we were the greatest.
Kesombongan di masa muda yang indah
Such youthful pride in those beautiful days.
Aku raja, kaupun raja
I am a king, and you are a king.
Aku hitam, kaupun hitam
I am black, and you are black.
Arti teman lebih dari sekedar materi
The meaning of friendship is more than just material wealth.
Pegang pundakku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold onto my shoulder, don't ever let go,
Bila ku mulai lelah
when I begin to grow tired,
Lelah dan tak bersinar
tired and losing my shine.
Remas sayapku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Squeeze my wings, don't ever let go,
Bila ku ingin terbang
when I want to fly,
Terbang meninggalkanmu
to fly and leave you behind.
Ku slalu membanggakanmu
I am always proud of you,
Kaupun slalu menyanjungku
and you always praise me.
Aku dan kamu darah abadi
You and I share eternal blood.
Demi bermain bersama
Just so we can play together,
Kita duakan segalanya
we cast everything else aside.
Merdeka kita, kita merdeka
We are independent, we are free.
Pegang pundakku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Hold onto my shoulder, don't ever let go,
Bila ku mulai lelah
when I begin to grow tired,
Lelah dan tak bersinar
tired and losing my shine.
Remas sayapku, jangan pernah lepaskan
Squeeze my wings, don't ever let go,
Bila ku ingin terbang
when I want to fly,
Terbang meninggalkanmu
to fly and leave you behind.
Tak pernah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
We never think about the end of this journey.
Tak usah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
No need for us to think about the end of this journey.
Dan tak usah kita pikirkan ujung perjalanan ini
And no need for us to think about the end of this journey.
Happy anniversary, Kaela!
Aku harus gimana?
What should I do?
Okay, that's kind of an easy trick.
So that's how these rooms work, huh?
I guess this door is locked too, right?
Okay.
I need to find a clue here and get out.
Hmm...
What am I supposed to do with this?
Coffee? Arrow, right? What?
Hmm...
There's another box, but I'm not the weak ones, so...
I have no idea.
Who's gonna judge me anyway if I open the next clue?
I just need to get out from here and leave this weird place,
or else I'll be late for my 3D.
Loncat, jalan kiri.
Jump, walk left.
Okay, udah, sana.
Okay, go there.
Satu, dua, tiga, loncat! Jalan kiri...
One, two, three, jump! Walk left...
Loncat! Jalan kanan...
Jump! Walk right...
Ngapain pula aku melompat?
Why did I jump anyway?
Loncat! Kiri lagi.
Jump! Left again.
Loncat! Gak... Ini yang penting bisa aja.
Jump! No... This is what matters to be able to do.
Kiri! Kiri! Kiri! Kiri!
Left! Left! Left! Left!
Eh?
I don't get it.
Oh! Kopikanan?!
Oh my...
What kind of clue is that?
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets,
Temani dalam kesendirianku
accompanying me in my solitude.
Menemani aku dalam kepedihan
Accompanying me in my pain,
Ini ku bertahan
here I endure.
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets,
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
giving a new spirit to my soul.
Beri kicauan merdu untuk hidupku
Giving a melodious chirp for my life,
Ini ku bertahan
here I endure.
Aku pasti bisa
I can definitely do it,
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
enjoying everything and facing it.
Aku yakin pasti...
I am sure, definitely...
...bisa
...I can.
Mentari terbenam
The sun sets,
Beri semangat baru untuk jiwaku
giving a new spirit to my soul.
Beri kicauan merdu untuk hidupku
Giving a melodious chirp for my life,
Ini ku bertahan
here I endure.
Aku pasti bisa
I can definitely do it,
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
enjoying everything and facing it.
Aku yakin pasti...
I am sure, definitely...
...bisa
...I can.
Aku pasti bisa
I can definitely do it,
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
enjoying everything and facing it.
Aku yakin pasti...
I am sure, definitely...
...bisa
...I can.
Aku ingin lepas
I want to let go
Seluruh bebanku
of all my burdens,
Dan kujalani hidupku
and live my life.
dengan senyuman
...with a smile.
Aku pasti bisa
I can definitely do it
Menikmati semua dan menghadapinya
Enjoying everything and facing it
Aku yakin pasti bisa
I'm sure I can definitely do it
Dan kujalani hidupku dengan senyuman
And I live my life with a smile
Oh... This room is...
...different?
Eh? Sleeping.
Does this thing know if I lied? Whatever, sleeping.
Ugh, stop asking me the same question! Sleeping! I love sleeping!
Is this some kind of joke?
My hobby is anything except answering the same questions over and over again.
Can the door just please open? I've had enough with this.
No, I refuse to answer.
Dahlah.
I give up.
Oh! Finally a different one and an easy one too! 8! Of course, 8!
広い宇宙の数ある一つ
In this wide universe, there is
青い地球の広い世界で
A big world on a blue earth...
小さな恋の思いは届く
A small memory of love will reach
小さな島のあなたのもとへ
You, who are living on a small island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Time has passed since I met you,
思いを込めた手紙もふえる
And the letters filled with my feelings increase.
いつしか二人互いに響く
Before we knew it, it's already echoing between us,
時に激しく 時に切なく
Sometimes intensely, sometimes painfully.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Echoing far away into the distance,
やさしい歌は世界を変える
This gentle love song will change the world.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
Look, the person who is important to you is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach only you...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
ほら
Look...
ほら 響け恋の歌
Look, let this love song echo!
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You realized, as the two of us walked...
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
Even on a dark path, the moon shines on us daily.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Without letting go of our tightly held hands,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
Our feelings are strong, swearing to eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
In the depths of forever, I'll definitely say...
思い変わらず同じ言葉を
These same words, with unchanged feelings.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Even then, it's not enough, turning into tears...
喜びになり
Turning into joy.
言葉にできず ただ抱きしめる ただ抱きしめる
Unable to put it into words, I'll just hold you close, just hold you close.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
Look, the person who is important to you is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach only you...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
ほら
Look...
ほら 響け恋の歌
Look, let this love song echo!
夢ならば覚めないで
If it's a dream, don't wake me up...
If it's a dream, don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の星となる
The time spent with you will become an everlasting star.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
Look, the person who is important to you is right beside you.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach only you...
響け恋の歌
Let this love song echo!
響け恋の歌 ほら
Echo, song of love! Look...
あなたにとって
...for you,
大事な人ほど すぐそばにいるの
the more important they are, the closer they are.
ただ あなたにだけ
Just...
届いて欲しい
...I want it to reach you.
響け恋の歌 ほら
Echo, song of love! Look...
ほら
Look...
響け恋の歌
Echo, song of love!
Eh? Ngulang apaan?
Eh? Repeat what?
Chaos?
Kepalaku emang lagi chaos sih, tapi maksudnya?
My mind is indeed in chaos, but what do you mean?
Meja murid ada 5, terus meja guru ada 1...
There are 5 student desks, and 1 teacher's desk...
Aku nggak paham.
I don't get it.
Hmm... chaos.
Eh?
Hakos Baelz?
Jangan-jangan maksudnya itu?
Could it be what I think it is?
JOONNN MY SOULLL!!! JOONNN MY SOULLL!!
Kok pintunya nggak kebuka?
Why isn't the door opening?
Oh! 10 kali!
Oh, 10 times!
Oke. JOONNN MY SOULLL 10 kali!
Okay. "JOONNN MY SOULLL" 10 times.
Eh, kayaknya bukan gitu, deh.
Wait, maybe not like that.
JOONNN MY SOULLL! JOONNN MY SOULLL! JOONNN MY SOULLL! JOONNN MY SOULLL!...
JOONNN MY SOULLL! JOONNN MY SOULLL! JOONNN MY SOULLL!
Nice.
Wanna be the Biggest Dreamer
全速力で未来も現在も駆け抜けろ
...running full speed through both the future and the present!
そう 僕らは気づいたんだ
That's right, I realized it.
ずっと宿題忘れてた
I forgot about my homework all along.
それはひとつの謎謎謎
That's a single riddle, riddle, riddle...
「僕は誰なんだろう?」
...of "who in the world am I?"
スライディングしてすりむけたヒザ痛くたってね
Even if my knees get scraped from sliding and it hurts,
すぐ立ち上がらなきゃ
I have to stand right back up...
チャンスは逃げてゆく分かってるさ
...or my chance will slip away, I know that.
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer!
夢見るコトがすべてはじまりそれが答えだろ
Dreaming is where it all begins, that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly farther than anyone,
すべての明日を貫いて
piercing through all of our tomorrows!
地平線まで飛んでゆけ
Fly all the way to the horizon!
羽をもらった勇気たち
O courage that has been granted wings,
強く大きくなるために
to grow strong and big...
僕も走りだそう
...I will start running too!
聞こえていたよカウントダウンずっと前から
I've been hearing the countdown for a long time.
準備はできてるさ
I'm already prepared,
今すぐはじめよう
let's begin right now...
ゼロに変われ!
...and transform into zero!
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer!
信じられなきゃ瞬きしてるセツナに消えるよ
If we don't believe, it'll vanish in the blink of an eye.
ココろの標的そらさず走れ
Run without losing sight of your heart's target,
すべてのチカラぶつけよう
let's throw in all of our strength!
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer!
夢見るコトがすべてはじまりそれが答えだろ
Dreaming is where it all begins, that's the answer, right?
誰より遠くへ飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly farther than anyone,
すべての明日を貫いて
piercing through all of our tomorrows!
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer!
夢見るコトが すべて始まり
Dreaming is the start of everything,
それが答えだろ
that's the answer.
誰より遠くへ飛んで見せるよ
I'll show you I can fly farther than anyone,
すべての明日を貫いて
piercing through all of tomorrow!
Big and Bigger, Biggest Dreamer!
夢見るコトが すべて始まり
Dreaming is the start of everything,
それが答えだろ
that's the answer.
Wanna be the Biggest Dreamer
全速力で未来も現在も駆け抜けろ
running full speed through both the future and the present!
A bomb now?
Okay, this is getting out of hand already.
I was supposed to be doing my 3D now...
...but somehow, I got lost and trapped in a room with a bomb...
...and I need to decipher Morse code.
What a fabulous day!
And a phone?
What am I supposed to do? Call YAGOO and tell him that I'm lost and ask for help?
Wait, I think I know what to do.
Ha, hello?
I'm lost, and I'm trapped with a bomb.
What?!
I hope you can solve a Morse code, or it's so over.
Huh?
Okay, dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dash-dot, dash-dot-dash-dash, dot-dash.
C... H... A...
Fast! It's gonna explode!
Can you repeat it again?
Dash-dot-dash, dot-dot-dot-dot, dot-dash, dash-dash, dash-dash-dash, dash-dot, dash-dot-dash-dash, dot-dash.
M... O... N... uhm...
What is Chamon? I think I'm gonna die.
I think the last one is Y... A...
Chamonya? What?
I don't know what you are doing, but good luck!
Thanks, bye!
Cha, Chamonya...
Chachamonya?
I really wanna be with you
I really wanna, really wanna, really wanna be with you
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear / So trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
I'll be そばにいるから
I'll be, because I'm by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も恐れないで
Trust me, don't be afraid of anything anymore
My dear みんな一緒で
My dear, we're all together
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて この温もり
Just keep feeling this warmth
ちゃんと聞こえている
I can clearly hear it
君の心 の声
the voice of your heart
小さな不安さえ 僕たちが看取ってあげる
We will take care of even your smallest anxieties
何度も伝えたい
I want to tell you over and over again
君は一人じゃない
You are not alone
変わることのない
There is an unchanging
愛はきっとここにある
love that is surely right here
泣いてみればいい
It's okay to try crying
頼ってみればいい
It's okay to try relying on us
そのすべてを
All of those things,
受け止めると決めた
I have decided to accept them
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, wherever you are
Call me 一つになれる
Call me, we can become one
Trust me この想い ほどけないから
Trust me, because these feelings won't unravel
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the burden you carry
Trust me 下ろしてみればいい
Trust me, it's okay to try putting it down
そう君のために僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for your sake
Really wanna be with you
Oh trust me, trust me, trust me, yeah
どれほどの悲しみ
How much sadness
君は隠してたの
were you hiding?
どれほどの想いを
How many feelings
胸に閉じ込めてきたの
did you keep locked up in your heart?
痛みと引き換えに
In exchange for pain,
手に入れた強さを
the strength you've gained
いつか優しさへ 君は変えてゆけるはず
you should be able to turn into kindness someday.
奪われたって
Even if it's taken away,
壊されたって
even if it's broken,
大事なのは 君らしくいること
what's important is staying true to yourself.
I'm here たとえ世界が
I'm here, even if the world
Call me 終わるとしても
Call me, even if it comes to an end
Trust me 繋ぐ手を離さないから
Trust me, because I will never let go of your hand
My dear いつまでも一緒で
My dear, we'll be together forever
Trust me 未来へ 歩き出そう
Trust me, let's walk towards the future
そう 君のために 僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for you
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も 恐れないで
Trust me, don't fear anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて このぬくもり
Just feel this warmth
いつまでもそばにいる forever
I'll always be by your side, forever
いつまでも離れない never ever
I'll never ever leave you, never ever
君がいれば whatever you do
As long as you are here, whatever you do
ねえ 僕に教えて whatever you say
Hey, tell me, whatever you say
痛いことあれば すべて飲み込み
If there are painful things, swallow them all
もしそれでも無理ならば 頼み込み
If it's still too much, rely on me
You're my love, you're my shine, you're my dear
世界敵に回しても trust me
Even if the world turns against us, trust me
泣いてみればいい
You should try crying
頼ってみればいい
You should try relying on me
そのすべてを 受け止めると決めた
I've decided to accept all of it
I'm here どこにいたって
I'm here, no matter where you are
Call me ひとつになれる
Call me, we can become one
Trust me この想いほどけないから
Trust me, because these feelings won't unravel
My dear 抱えた荷物
My dear, the burden you carry
Trust me おろしてみればいい
Trust me, you should try letting it down
そう 君のために 僕がいるんだ
Yes, I am here for you
I'm here そばにいるから
I'm here, because I'm by your side
Call me 僕がいるから
Call me, because I am here
Trust me もう何も 恐れないで
Trust me, don't fear anything anymore
My dear 見えない糸で
My dear, with an invisible thread
Trust me 繋がっているから
Trust me, because we are connected
ただ感じていて このぬくもり
Just feel this warmth
With me もう離れないで
With me, don't leave anymore
Give me 心をひらいて
Give me, open your heart
Feel me すべてを伝えて
Feel me, convey everything to me
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
With me 言葉はいらない
With me, we don't need words
Give me 見つめ合えばいい
Give me, we just need to look at each other
Feel me すべてを預けて
Feel me, entrust everything to me
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Trust me, baby, oh...
Yeah, yeah...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
Hello? Anybody here?
Okay, I have played enough horror games, and I don't know why...
but it reminds me of something similar.
Should I read this? Maybe?
何が目的ですか
What is your purpose?
何でいるんですか
Why are you here?
キレてますか
Are you angry?
怒ってますか
Are you mad?
ここにいていいですか
Can I stay here?
戻ります
I'm coming back.
帰りましょうか
Shall we go home?
戻ろうか
Shall we head back?
何すればいい
What should I do?
何か手伝えますか
Can I help you with anything?
敵意はありますか
Are you hostile?
何者ですか
What are you?
どこにいますか
Where are you?
近くにいますか
Are you close?
出てきて
Come out.
アピールしてください
Please give us a sign.
もしもし
Hello?
Okay...
That door looks similar to the entrance door.
Is that the exit?
Or is that a trap?
Well, if this is a horror game...
Should I try to scream?
AAAAAHHH!!!
Shut up!
Eh?
そうさ 悲しみをやさしさに
That's right, turn sadness into kindness
自分らしさを力に
Turn your uniqueness into strength
迷いながらでもいい
It's okay to get lost
歩き出して
Begin walking
もう一回
Once again
誰かの期待にずっと応え
To always answer everyone's expectations
褒められるのが好きなのですか？
Is it because you like to be praised?
なりたい自分を摺り替えても
Even if you swap your true self with what you want to be
笑顔はいつでも素敵ですか？
Will your smile always be beautiful?
始まりだけ
Just dreaming of the beginning
夢見て起きる
Then waking up
その先なら
If there's more after that
いつか
Someday...
自分の腕で
With my own arms
そうだ 大事な物はいつも 形のない物だけ
That's right, the most important thing is always without any shape
ものだけ
only those things.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if you obtain them or lose them,
気づかぬまま
you remain unaware.
そうさ 悲しみを やさしさに
Yes, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを 力に
your uniqueness into strength.
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's okay to get lost, so begin walking.
もう一回
Once again,
once again.
誰かの期待にずっと応え
Do you like to be praised by always
褒められるのが好きなのですか
answering everyone's expectations?
自分を素直に出せなくなって
Making you unable to be honest with yourself,
傷つけながらすぐに尖って
and sharp right away when getting hurt.
新しい風
Take the new wind...
味方につけて
...as your ally.
探していていいんだ
It's okay to search for it...
いつか
...someday.
青い鳥を
The blue bird...
そうだ 大事なものは いつも
That's right, the most important thing is always
形のないものだけ
something without any shape.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if you obtain it or lose it,
気づかぬまま
you remain unaware.
そうさ 悲しみを やさしさに
Yes, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを 力に
your uniqueness into strength.
迷いながらでもいい 歩き出して
It's okay to get lost, so begin walking.
涙の後は なぜか吹っ切れてた
After the tears, somehow I felt free.
空に虹が出るように 自然なこと
Like a rainbow appearing in the sky, it's natural.
雨は上がった
The rain has cleared.
だから
Therefore,
大事なものは いつも
the most important thing is always
形のないものだけ
something without any shape.
手に入れても なくしても
Even if you obtain it or lose it,
気づかぬまま
you remain unaware.
そうさ 悲しみを やさしさに
Yes, turn sadness into kindness,
自分らしさを 力に
your uniqueness into strength.
君ならきっとやれる
Believe that you can surely do it
信じていて
if it's you.
もう一回
Once again,
once again.
もう一回
Once again,
もういいかい
are you ready?
小さな頃には
In my childhood,
宝の地図が
a treasure map
頭の中に
inside my head
浮かんでいて
was floating around.
いつでも探した
I always searched
奇跡の場所を
for the place of miracles,
知らない誰かに
so that I wouldn't lose
負けないように
to someone I didn't know.
今では
Now...
ほこりだらけの毎日
...in these dust-covered days,
いつの日か
one day,
すべての
I'll just...
時に身を任せるだけ
...leave everything to time.
もしも世界が 変わるのなら
If the world were to change,
何も知らない 頃の私に
to the me who knew nothing back then...
連れていって
take me back,
思い出が
so that my memories...
色あせないように
...won't fade away.
小さな頃から歌を歌って
Ever since I was little, I've been singing songs,
夢見る心 温めてた
keeping my dreaming heart warm.
みんなで真似した いびつのメロディ
The distorted melody we all copied...
今度は遠くに聴こえるより
instead of hearing it from afar this time...
今ではため息ついてばかりで
Now, I do nothing but sigh,
誰もまだ本当の夢さえ掴めないまま
with everyone still unable to grasp their true dreams.
もしも時代が戻るのなら
If only time could turn back,
涙をした頃の私に
to the time when I shed tears,
連れて行って 切なさが追いつかないように
take me back, so that this pain won't catch up to me.
もしも世界が変わるのなら
If only the world could change,
何も知らない頃の私に
to the time when I knew nothing,
連れて行って 思い出が色褪せないように
take me back, so that my memories won't fade away.
連れて行って 切なさが追いつかないように
Take me back, so that this pain won't catch up to me.
Why does everything feel so real?
Am I real?
Can you even feel my existence?
Is this what deja vu looks like?
Is this what déjà vu looks like?
All these memories mean the world to me.
Thank you for walking this journey with me.
Let's make more! :3
Like! comments! share! subscribe!